// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "What is a stack in data structure?",
      answer: "A linear data structure",
      options: [
        "A linear data structure",
        "A non-linear data structure",
        "A hierarchical data structure",
        "An abstract data type"
      ]
    },
  
  
      {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which operation in a stack adds an element to the top of the stack?",
      answer: "Push",
      options: [
        "Pop",
        "Push",
        "Peek",
        "Swap"
      ]
    },
    
   
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "In a stack, which item is considered the first to be removed (Last-In, First-Out)?",
      answer: "Top element",
      options: [
        "Top element",
        "Bottom element",
        "Middle element",
        "Random element"
      ]
    },
     
  
      {
      numb: 4,
      question: "What is the time complexity for the push operation in a stack with n elements?",
      answer: "O(1)",
      options: [
        "O(n)",
        "O(log n)",
        "O(1)",
        "O(n^2)"
      ]
    },
   
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following data structures can be used to implement a stack?",
      answer: "Array",
      options: [
        "Queue",
        "Array",
        "Linked List",
        "Tree"
      ]
    },
     
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the term for a situation where a stack is full and cannot accommodate any more elements?",
    answer: "Stack overflow",
    options: [
      "Stack overflow",
      "Stack underflow",
      "Stack exhaustion",
      "Stack imbalance"
    ]
  },
   
  
  
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which stack operation retrieves the top element without removing it?",
  answer: "Peek",
  options: [
    "Push",
    "Pop",
    "Peek",
    "Clear"
  ]
  },
     
  
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Which data structure is used to efficiently implement the stack data structure?",
  answer: "Array",
  options: [
    "Queue",
    "Linked List",
    "Array",
    "Heap"
  ]
  },
  
     
  
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "What happens when you try to pop an element from an empty stack?",
  answer: "Stack underflow",
  options: [
    "Stack overflow",
    "Stack underflow",
    " Stack imbalance",
    "Stack lock"
  ]
  },
     
  
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: " Which of the following is not a valid stack operation?",
  answer: "Insert",
  options: [
    "Push",
    "Pop",
    "Insert",
    "Clear"
  ]
  }
      
  ];